We fall apart to come together.
Mr. Roosevelt is a comedy film directed by Noël Wells.
A young woman returns home and must confront her
ex-boyfriend when an unexpected tragedy occurs.
Emily Martin, played by Noël Wells.
Eric Kline, played by Nick Thune.
Celeste Jones, played by Britt Lower.
Jen Morales, played by Daniella Pineda.
Art, played by Andre Hyland.
Todd, played by Doug Benson.
Roosevelt is an American comedy film written,
directed by, and starring Noël Wells.
The film marks her directorial debut and also stars Nick Thune, Britt Lower, Daniella
Pineda, Andre Hyland, Doug Benson, Armen Weitzman, and Sergio Cilli.
The plot follows Emily Martin (Noël Wells) as she returns to her hometown to say goodbye to her cat, and
attempts to come to terms with her past while staying with her ex-boyfriend and his new girlfriend.
Roosevelt premiered at South by Southwest on March 12, 2017 and
was released by Paladin on November 22, 2017.
The film received positive reviews from critics.
The tone is lighthearted.